In many interviews and in many universities, you are asked to get the length of link, at least to
write a method that get the length of an ink list.
So we will create a method called get length.
It's a returning type, is integer and took into the meter.
There refers to the hat structure note stamp hat, so start by struct note stamp equal to the head.
We create this.
This linked list and we create a variable called count.
It's an orange.
Or in in yellow.
This is the counter, it's a memory and the structure note, this is the linked list.
We have five elements.
We start by making the hat equal to temp.
OK, so we are signing to have that now we start while temp does not equal to none.
So the reference is not.
It is referencing and pointing to the non we increase count by one.
OK.
And Temp two the next again temp does not equal to null, so move the cursor count increased by one.
Then stamp referencing to knowledge, no.
So move the cursor by one.
Again, the while loop count increased by one and Trump is referencing to null.
Yes, it's referencing so it will break out the loop and return the count.
So we have reached here their stamp, referencing the they're not the next, not word of forensic or
this, not is their forensic or not.
So the count now would be returned as five.
So we have increased the count five times, according to this wire loop, and we return the count equal
to five.
It's very simple.
This is the way how to get the length of that.
Think at least the next example?
We will get the middle note of link at and.